# REXHENS BALLA







rexhensb3@gmail.com



+355684816604

# ABOUT MY CAREER

As a current student in second year, I have gained a solid foundation in programming through my academic studies. However, I understand that practical experience is essential in the field of programming. To supplement my academic studies, I have actively sought out opportunities to gain practical experience. I have built my own projects, attended coding events and seminars, and practiced on coding platforms. Through these experiences, I have honed my skills in programming and gained valuable exposure to real-world projects. I always want to be one step ahead!

### WORK EXPERIENCE

- .NET Developer Internship at IkubInfo 12/2023 - 02/2024
  - IT Supervisor at INSTAT 09/2023 - 12/2023 IT Support at INSTAT 07/2023 - 09/2023
- **International Virtual Internship** 03/2023 - 04/2023

# ACADEMIC BACKGROUND



IkubInfo Academy - C#, .NET Bootcamp



Albania ICT Academy - Python Certified



Epoka University – Ba. in Software Engineering



Petro Nini Luarasi High School

# **EXTRACURRICULUM ACTIVITIES**

- Junction Hackathon
- Google Developers Club Core Team
- Organising DevFest Albania 2023
- Instructor at CFA (Code For Albania)

### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

#### Java

FX, Join-Fork Frameworks

#### C# - .NET Core

Entity, Identity Frameworks

#### Software Architecture

3 Layered Architecture

#### **Design Patterns**

MVC, REST API

### **Software Testing**

Unit Testing, Integration Testing

#### **Software Modeling**

ERD. RS. Activity. Class Diagrams

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Dedication

**Quick Learning** 

**Problem Solving** 

**Time Management** 

**Teamwork** 

# LANGUAGES

English - Full Professional - Aptis Certified

Italian - Intermediate Level

Albanian- Native

# **Certifications**

• Certificate of completition International Virtual Internship by Vodafone

• Certificate of competition by Albania ICT – Python Programming Language

• Certificate of completion by Datamax & Holberton School in Introduction to Machine Learning

• Certificate of completion by Epoka University in Excel Workshop

• Certificate of Bootcamp Completition C#, .NET Framework

• Certificate of competition Junction Hackathon